<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="stylesheet.xsl"?>
<tvshows>
    <show class="table">
        <tableheader>
            <header class="Dataheader">Title</header>
            <header class="Dataheader">Genre</header>
            <header class="Dataheader">Rating</header>
            <header class="Dataheader">Description</header>
            <header class="Dataheader">Plot</header>
            <header class="Dataheader">Link</header>
        </tableheader>
        <show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">Black Rider</title>
            <genre class="Datarow">Drama, Action</genre>
            <rating class="Datarow">12.5%</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">Elias' family falls victim to the ruthless Golden Scorpion 
                syndicate, leaving him as the sole survivor and sparking his unyielding quest for justice. 
                Embracing the ancient martial art of Kali, he metamorphoses into the “Black Rider,” 
                a beacon of hope in a city plagued by corruption and lawlessness.</description>
            <plot class="Datarow">A delivery driver becomes a vigilante on his motorcycle and faces a 
                powerful  crime syndicate that threatens his city.</plot>
            <link id="clickable" class="Datarow" href="https://www.gmanetwork.com/fullepisodes/home/black_rider" >https://www.gmanetwork.com/fullepisodes/home/black_rider</link>
            <image class="Datarow" href="image/blackrider.jpeg"></image>
        </show_list>
        <show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">Batang Quiapo</title>
            <genre class="Datarow">Crime Drama Action Comedy Syndicate</genre>
            <rating class="Datarow">9.5%</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">FPJ's Batang Quiapo (transl. FPJ's Quiapo Kid) is a Philippine action-comedy drama 
                television series broadcast by Kapamilya Channel. Directed by Malu L. Sevilla, Darnel Joy R. Villaflor, Coco Martin 
                and Kevin de Vela, the series stars Martin as the titular main character. It is based on the 1986 action-comedy film 
                of the same title starring Fernando Poe Jr. and Maricel Soriano.The series premiered on the network's Primetime Bida 
                evening block, and worldwide via The Filipino Channel on February 13, 2023, replacing Mars Ravelo's Darna.</description>
            <plot class="Datarow">A young man named Tanggol (Coco Martin) rises to be one of the biggest outlaws in the 
                neighborhood while he navigates his way in life to survive in Quiapo, Manila. Hoping to earn the affection 
                of his parents, his feat draws him closer to the truth about his identity</plot>
            <link id="clickable" class="Datarow" href="https://ent.abs-cbn.com/batangquiapo">https://ent.abs-cbn.com/batangquiapo</link>
            <image class="Datarow" href="image/batangquiapo.jpg"></image>
        </show_list>
        <show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">TVJ</title>
            <genre class="Datarow">Comedy</genre>
            <rating class="Datarow">3.3%</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">TVJ is the initialism of the comedy trio composed of Tito Sotto, Vic Sotto, and Joey de Leon. 
                The trio has been active in the Philippine entertainment industry since 1972, and is best remembered for their multimedia 
                comedy ventures in music, film, and television. Their hallmark styles are slapstick comedy, parodies, observational comedy, 
                wordplays, and pop culture commentary. Early film posters and album covers often credit the trio as Tito, Vic and Joey and 
                not by the initialism</description>
            <plot class="Datarow"></plot>
            <link class="Datarow" href="https://www.tv5.com.ph/shows/e-a-t">https://www.tv5.com.ph/shows/e-a-t</link>
            <image class="Datarow1" href="image/TVJ.jpg"> </image>
        </show_list>
		<show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">Wednesday</title>
            <genre class="Datarow">Horror Comedy Drama Adventure Fantasy Mystery Crime Fiction</genre>
            <rating class="Datarow">8.1/10</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">The show follows Wednesday's years as a student at Nevermore Academy, her parents' 
				alma mater, as she tries to master her psychic ability, thwart a killing spree that has terrorized the local town, 
				and solve the supernatural mystery that embroiled her parents 25 years ago.
			</description>
            <plot class="Datarow">Follows Wednesday Addams' years as a student, when she attempts to master her emerging psychic ability, 
                thwart a killing spree, and solve the mystery that embroiled her parents. A sleuthing, supernaturally infused mystery charting 
                Wednesday Addams' years as a student at Nevermore Academy.</plot>
            <link class="Datarow" href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt13443470/">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt13443470/</link>
            <image class="Datarow" href="image/wednesday.jpg"></image>
        </show_list>
		<show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">Stranger Things</title>
            <genre class="Datarow">science fiction horror drama</genre>
            <rating class="Datarow">8.7/10</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">When a young boy vanishes, a small town uncovers a mystery involving secret experiments, 
				terrifying supernatural forces and one strange little girl.
			</description>
            <plot class="Datarow">Set in the 1980s, the series centers around the residents of the fictional small town of Hawkins, Indiana, 
                as they are plagued by a hostile alternate dimension known as the Upside Down, after a nearby human experimentation facility 
                opens a gateway between Earth and the Upside Down.</plot>
            <link class="Datarow" href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt4574334/">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt4574334/</link>
            <image class="Datarow" href="image/stranger_things.jpg"></image>
        </show_list>
		<show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">Larong Pusit</title>
            <genre class="Datarow">Horror Action Thriller Romance Drama Comedy War Western</genre>
            <rating class="Datarow">8.0/10</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">The story revolves around a group of cash-strapped people from all backgrounds and ages who 
				are invited to participate in a survival game with a top prize of 45.6 billion Won (around USD 35 million). The players 
				are abducted from the streets of South Korea and crowded together on an island where only one survivor will win the ultimate prize: 
				their lives and the money to pay their crippling debts.
			</description>
            <plot class="Datarow"></plot>
            <link class="Datarow" href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt10919420/">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt10919420/</link>
            <image class="Datarow" href="image/squid_games.jpg"></image>
        </show_list>
		<show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">Arcane</title>
            <genre class="Datarow">	Action Adventure Drama Science fantasy Steampunk</genre>
            <rating class="Datarow">9.0/10</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">The story revolves around the sisters Vi and Jinx, who were separated as young children in the undercity, 
				Zaun. The show explores the delicate balance between the rich city of Piltover and the seedy underbelly of Zaun.
			</description>
            <plot class="Datarow"></plot>
            <link class="Datarow" href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt11126994/">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt11126994/</link>
            <image class="Datarow" href="image/arcane.png"></image>
        </show_list>
		<show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">Loki</title>
            <genre class="Datarow"> Action Drama Superhero Adventure Thriller Mystery</genre>
            <rating class="Datarow"> 8.2/10</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">After taking the Tesseract in "Avengers: Endgame," a parallel Loki is transported before the Time Variance 
				Authority, which oversees the timeline. Loki must choose between erasure as a "time variation" or fixing the timeline to stop a bigger threat.
			</description>
            <plot class="Datarow"></plot>
            <link class="Datarow" href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt9140554/">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt9140554/</link>
            <image class="Datarow" href="image/2Loki.jpg"></image>
        </show_list>
		<show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">Game of Thrones</title>
            <genre class="Datarow">Serial Action Drama Suspense Tragedy Fantasy Romance </genre>
            <rating class="Datarow">9.2/10</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">After taking the Tesseract in "Avengers: Endgame," a parallel Loki is transported before the Time Variance Authority, 
				which oversees the timeline. Loki must choose between erasure as a "time variation" or fixing the timeline to stop a bigger threat.
			</description>
            <plot class="Datarow">Set on the fictional continents of Westeros and Essos, Game of Thrones has a large ensemble cast and follows several story arcs 
                throughout the course of the show. The first major arc concerns the Iron Throne of the Seven Kingdoms of Westeros through a web of political conflicts 
                among the noble families either vying to claim the throne or fighting for independence from whoever sits on it. The second focuses on the last descendant 
                of the realm's deposed ruling dynasty, who has been exiled to Essos and is plotting to return and reclaim the throne. The third follows the Night's Watch, 
                a military order defending the realm against threats from beyond Westeros' northern border.</plot>
            <link class="Datarow" href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0944947/">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0944947/</link>
            <image class="Datarow" href="image/Game_of_Thrones.png"></image>
        </show_list>
		<show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">Black Knight</title>
            <genre class="Datarow">Action Adventure Sci-Fi Thriller Drama </genre>
            <rating class="Datarow">6.4/10</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">"Black Knight" is a science fiction series based on Lee Yoon-gyun's webtoon "Delivery Knight". The show is set in a 
				dystopian future where air pollution has ravaged most of the Earth, leaving only a small population left. The Black Knights, a group of elite
				delivery drivers, are essential for humanity's survival.
			</description>
            <plot class="Datarow">where people depend on respirator masks to breathe. Only one percent of the human race has survived, and a strict social stratification 
                has been established in the deserted lands of the Korean Peninsula. Delivery drivers play a crucial role within this system, and for refugees, becoming a 
                delivery driver is their only hope for survival.</plot>
            <link class="Datarow" href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt17013106/">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt17013106/</link>
            <image class="Datarow" href="image/Black_Knight.jpg"></image>
        </show_list>
		<show_list>
            <title class="Datarow">Prison Break</title>
            <genre class="Datarow">Serial Action Drama Suspense Adventure Mystery Crime-Fiction</genre>
            <rating class="Datarow">8.3/10</rating>
            <description class="Datarow">The story revolves around two brothers, Lincoln Burrows and Michael Scofield, who are framed for the murder of the 
				Vice President's brother and are awaiting execution on death row.
			</description>
            <plot class="Datarow">The story revolves around a man who was sentenced to death for a crime he did not commit and his brother's elaborate plan to help him escape his death sentence.</plot>
            <link class="Datarow" href="https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0455275/">https://www.imdb.com/title/tt0455275/</link>
            <image class="Datarow" href="image/Prison_Break.jpg"></image>
        </show_list>
    </show>
</tvshows>